Guide to A. Michael Noll Papers RG.047
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
- Series X: RISD 2025 Accretion
  - American Algorists, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - ASCI Bell Labs & the Origins of the Multimedia Artist, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Academy Schloss Solitude. Stuggart Germany., 2004-2014 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - ASCI Bell Labs & The Origins of the Multimedia Artist, 1998-2014 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Nam June Paik, 2014-2020 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Gaussian-Quadratic, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Computer Composition with Lines, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Vertical-Horizontal, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Sinusoids, Undated (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - General Articles & Paper @ Art & Animation, 1962-2016 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - IBM Computers and Art, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous Pamphlets + CD, 1965-2019 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Technical Memorandum, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Negative Comments on 1965 Noll Paper by AT&T's H.M. Craig, 1965-1966 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - 4D Computer Animated Films, 1967-2022 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Correspondance @ Computer Art, 1996-2014 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Wise 50th Wise, 1965-2014 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Michael Noll and Computer Art, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Computer Graphics + Computer Art Herbert W. Franke, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Negatives, 1965-1971 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Howard Wise Negatives, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Effects of Artistic Training on Aesthetic Preferences for Pseudo-Random Computer-Generated Patterns, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Originals, 35mm 3D Stereo Pairs, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Sinusoids, 2 different versions 35mm originals, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - 4D Hyper Movie, Undated (Box 12)
  - HYPEROBJECTS, Undated (Box 12)
  - Originals, Variations on [indecipherable], Undated (Box 12)
  - Slides, Undated (Box 12)
  - Slide Talks, Box 1, 1960 (Box 12)
  - Slide Talks, Box 2, 1960 (Box 12)